<DialogueTree xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/dialogue_schema.xsd">
	<NameField>Samster68</NameField>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>Entry</Name>
		<EntryCondition>DEFAULT</EntryCondition>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Welcome to the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Outer Wilds Mod Museum</color>]]>!</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		<DialogueOptionsList>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>Who are you?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>1</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>When are you updating Hearthian Golf?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>2</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>How can I help with the Mod Museum?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>3</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
			<DialogueOption>
				<Text>I'm going to look around.</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>4</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
		</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>
	
	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>1</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>My name is Samster68, and I'm the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Mod Museum Administrator</color>]]>. I'm in charge of maintaining and expanding the museum.</Page>
			<Page>All exhibits and characters going in and out of the museum have to go through me first. I keep pretty extensive records.</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		<DialogueTarget>Entry</DialogueTarget>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>2</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Ah, Hearthian Golf... the black sheep of the Samster68 tetralogy. Even though I am passionate about the mod, I did a terrible job on its launch.</Page>
			<Page>However, the entirety of the next update is already planned out. I would love to give it a quick polish before hosting a tourney or something. I think it would be a lot of fun! The whole purpose of Hearthian Golf was to provide more activities for Quantum Space Buddies.</Page>
			<Page>If the event goes well, I will execute my plans to give the mod a huge overhall and add more content.</Page>
			<Page>Let me know if that interests you!</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		<DialogueTarget>Entry</DialogueTarget>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>3</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Thank you for asking! I will need as much help as I can get.</Page>
			<Page>If you are already on the <![CDATA[<color=orange>Outer Wilds Modding Discord</color>]]>, you can reach out to me there. There you can find a list of ways you can help out, as well as chat with other incredible mod developers!</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		<DialogueTarget>Entry</DialogueTarget>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>4</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Enjoy your time at the museum!</Page>
		</Dialogue>
	</DialogueNode>

</DialogueTree>